newyorkcitytheatre.com 2019-05-26

# New York City Theater - Privacy Policy

**Version 2.1**   
Last updated 21 September 2018

Thanks for using [New York City Theater](https://www.newyorkcitytheatre.com/)! We continue to be committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, and this Privacy Policy sets out more clearly how your data is handled.

## 1\. Who we are and what services we offer

New York City Theater is a complete, impartial guide to all the theatrical, musical and other performance arts events and venues in New York. New York City Theater is part of the Theatreland collection and is owned and operated by Theatreland Ltd, a company registered in the United Kingdom under company number 6859176. Theatreland’s address is 64 Kimber Road, London SW18 4PP, United Kingdom. Theatreland acts as a data controller with respect to the personal data discussed in this policy. Being a data controller simply means we determine the purposes and means of processing your personal data.

As well as experiencing our amazing performance arts coverage on New York City Theater, you might make use of our other offerings like purchasing theatre tickets, booking pre-theatre dining, parking for your event or even an overnight stay. If you need help with any of your purchases you might contact our helpdesk and if you feel like sharing you might write a review on site or share some of our content on your favourite social media platform. In this document, these and other similar usages of New York City Theater are referred to as our Services, and references to “we”, “us” and “our” refer to New York City Theater as operated by Theatreland Limited.

If you have any questions or concerns about your data, please contact our Data Protection Officer on privacy@theatrelandltd.com. This email inbox is proactively monitored, so you can confidently expect your query to be addressed. We aim to respond to enquiries within 30 working days but will usually be in touch much sooner.

## 2\. Who should read this

This Privacy Policy is relevant for anyone visiting our websites, using our Services or otherwise interacting with us.

## 3\. What personal data about you we collect and process

When you use our Services, you provide us with certain personal data.

We divide this data into “Required Data” (information essential for us to provide you with our Services), “Optional Data” (other information about you that you might supply but which is not required in order to use our Services) and “Publication Data” (information that you provide for the express purpose of publishing on the internet).

What data we hold and the basis for holding it varies by which of our Services you use

If you signed up for one of our email newsletters when you purchased from us or through our dedicated sign-up forms then this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can send you emails. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address

#### Optional Data

You may also choose to provide us with extra personal data in order to enhance the way we communicate with you. You can use our regular Services without providing this data, but if you do provide it, it will be treated with exactly the same care as your other personal data. These kinds of data include but are not limited to:

  * Your first and last name: so that we can talk to you personally
  * Your city, state/province/region or county: so that we can better tailor our content
  * Your Interests: so that we can better target out content
  * Which emails you’d like to receive:  so you only get what you ask for

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using or how you interact with our emails, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

If you signed up for one of our email or sms ticket availability alerts through our dedicated sign-up forms then this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can send you these alert messages. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your name, and email address AND/OR Your mobile telephone number  (for you to receive the email or SMS alert as appropriate)
  * Which show performance you want ticket alerts for (allows us to send you the correct communications!)

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using or how you interact with our emails, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

If you created a My Theatreland user account on our website, then this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can provide you with a user account on New York City Theater and provide the related services that go with that. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address (never revealed to anyone outside of our business)

  * A password (never revealed to anyone)

#### Optional Data

You may also choose to provide us with extra personal data in order to enhance the way we provide this Service for you. You can use our regular Services without providing this data, but if you do provide it, it will be treated with exactly the same care as your other personal data. These kinds of data include but are not limited to:

  * Your first and last name: so that we can talk to you personally
  * Your city, state/province/region or county: so that we can better tailor our content
  * Your Interests: so that we can better target out content
  * Which emails you’d like to receive:  so you only get what you ask for

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using or how often you interact with our emails, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

If you purchased tickets through our website or one of our ticket fulfillment partners then this is you!

#### Required Data

We, in conjunction with our ticket fulfillment partners, collect some personal data from you in order to complete your transaction. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address
  * Your address : in order to process your order and deliver your tickets if applicable
  * Your payment details (never stored, only passed securely to the relevant payment provider to authorise payment)

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is the legal contract for sale that we enter into with you._

If you’ve contacted us about promoting your products or advertising on our site then this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can liaise with you about your promotional or advertising needs. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address (never revealed to anyone outside of our business)
  * Your first and last name: so that we know who to deal with for the query
  * What company you represent if relevant: so that we know how best to address your query
  * What your query is about so that we can assign the correct team member to deal with your request.

#### Optional Data

You may also choose to provide us with extra personal data in order to enhance the way we communicate with you. You can use our regular Services without providing this data, but if you do provide it, it will be treated with exactly the same care as your other personal data. These kinds of data include but are not limited to:

  * Your job title
  * Your company website
  * Your address, city, state, zip/postal code, country

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent as well as the legal contract for services if one is entered into._

If you’ve submitted a review for a show on our site, then this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can display your review on our website. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your review title, summary and rating (which may contain your personal information if you choose to add it)

#### Optional Data

You may also choose to provide us with extra personal data in order to enhance the way we present your review on site. You can use our regular Services without providing this data, but if you do provide it, it will be treated with exactly the same care as your other personal data. These kinds of data include but are not limited to:

  * Your name so that we can personalise your review
  * Your location so other site users can see where the review was written from

#### Publication Data

As part of submitting a review on New York City Theater, you may choose to post otherwise private personal information into locations visible to all New York City Theater visitors. These locations include but are not limited to:

  * Homepage
  * Venue pages
  * Event pages
  * Review summary pages
  * Email newsletters
  * Social media pages

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

If you’ve entered a competition we’ve run through email, facebook or some other platform this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can enter you into the relevant competition. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address (never revealed to anyone outside of our business)
  * Your first and last name: so that we can talk to you personally
  * Your qualifying answer: in order to ensure that you are eligible to win
  * 

#### Publication Data

As part of entering a competition run by New York City Theater, you may choose to post otherwise private personal information into locations visible to all New York City Theater visitors. These locations could include but are not limited to:

  * Homepage
  * Venue pages
  * Event pages
  * Review summary pages
  * Email newsletters
  * Social Media Pages

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

If you’ve contacted our customer support helpdesk or communicated with us through other communications channels such as online forms, direct email, live chat, social media platforms, telephone or any other communications medium, this is you!

#### Required Data

We collect some personal data from you so that we can appropriately deal with your request. We don’t ask for more data than we need in order to provide our Services to you. The minimum personal data required for us to deliver our Services includes:

  * Your email address (never revealed to anyone outside of our business)

  * Your full name
  * Your Order ID if applicable
  * The content of your communication/request may contain personal information

#### Optional Data

You may also choose to provide us with extra personal data in order to enhance the way we deal with your request. You can use our regular Services without providing this data, but if you do provide it, it will be treated with exactly the same care as your other personal data. These kinds of data include but are not limited to:

  * Your telephone number if we need to talk to communicate with you by phone

#### Publication Data

If you communicate with us on an open public platform such as our public Twitter or Facebook feeds any information you provide will be in the public domain.

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

_The legal basis for us collecting, processing and storing this data is your consent._

This applies to anyone that visits our websites, so this is you!

As a general website user we clearly don’t directly collect any information from you, but in order for us to deliver our Services to you we collect some indirect information  as part of our legitimate interest in running our business.

#### Indirect data

Additionally, we will collect indirect information about you as part of providing our Services to you, such as the kind of web browser you are using, as part of our legitimate interest in delivering our Services and running our business. Please see “Indirect Collection” and “What we do with your personal information” below for more information on what kinds of data might be collected and used indirectly.

## 4\. How we collect your data

When you visit our websites, use our Services or otherwise interact with us you’ll provide us with your personal information directly at the time that you use the Service **"Direct Collection"** , we also collect other information necessary for delivering our Services to you and for maintaining the performance of our Services indirectly, which although collected through standard industry practice, may not be necessarily obvious to users without technical knowledge **"Indirect Collection"**

When you visit our websites, use our Services or otherwise interact with us you’ll provide us with your personal information directly at the time that you use the Service.  This will typically be done in the following circumstances:

  * On the sign up forms when signing up for newsletters or ticket alerts
  * When creating a My Theatreland user account
  * During the checkout process when purchasing items from us or one of our ticket fulfilment partners
  * When contacting us through our promotions & advertising forms
  * When writing a review for one of our shows
  * When submitting a helpdesk query or entering a competition

You might also provide personal data in other circumstances such as when you:

  * Send an email directly to one of our email addresses
  * Call us on our call center numbers
  * Chat to us using live chat

If you are under 13 years old, you must ensure that you have your parent or guardian’s consent to use our Services.

In addition to the information we collect directly from you, we also collect other information necessary for delivering our Services to you and for maintaining the performance of our Services. This information is collected in ways that are standard industry practice but not necessarily obvious to users without technical knowledge, and which may change from time to time.

#### Account related information

This is collected in association with you using our Services, such as when you are on our site or app or send an information or customer support request. It includes notes and details around your support requests.

#### Cookies and similar technologies

We use cookies and similar technologies on our website and mobile app to:

  * Make our shopping basket and checkout work
  * Determine whether you are logged in or not
  * Record some of your preferences (such as what country you’re in, what shows you’re interested in etc)
  * Track your browsing behaviour and device type
  * Collect various data, including analytics, about how you use New York City Theater
  * Localise content to make it relevant to where you are located
  * Analyse and improve the performance of our Services

Insofar as these cookies are not strictly necessary for the provision of our Services, we will ask you to consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website or when you install our mobile app. To learn more about how we use cookies, please read our [Cookie Policy](https://www.newyorkcitytheatre.com/privacy-cookies/).

#### Data about Usage of Services

This data is automatically collected when you use and interact with our Services. It includes log files, metadata, location information and  cookie/device IDs. This information includes specific data about your interactions with the features,, Internet Protocol (IP) address, information about browser configuration and plugins, browser type and settings, content and links (including those of third-parties, such as social media plugins) contained within the Services, the date and time the Services were used, language preferences and cookie data, information about devices accessing the Services, including type of device, what operating system is used, device settings, application IDs, unique device identifiers and error data, and some of this data collected might be capable of and be used to approximate your location.

#### Data provided by someone else

Someone else might provide us with personal data about you. For example, if you purchase tickets through us, our ticket fulfillment partners or payment providers will provide details of your order and payments status.  In circumstances like these where others give us information about you, or you provide us with personal information about others, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## 5\. What we do with your personal information

We strongly believe in both minimising the data we collect and limiting its use and purpose to only that (1) for which we have been given permission, (2) as necessary to deliver the Services you interact with, or (3) as we might be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. These uses include:

We collect various information relating your interactions with our Services. We utilise this information to:

  * Enable you to use our Services
  * Operate our website and mobile app
  * Ensure the security of our Services
  * Improve and optimise the operation and performance of our Services (including our websites and mobile applications)
  * Diagnose problems with and identify any security risks, errors, or needed enhancements to the Services
  * Detect and prevent fraud and abuse of our Services and systems
  * Collecting aggregate statistics about use of the Services
  * Understand and analyze how you use our Services and what products and services are most relevant to you

Often, much of the data collected is aggregated or statistical data about how individuals use our Services, and is not linked to any personal data, but to the extent it is itself personal data, or is linked or linkable to personal data, we treat it accordingly.

You’re able to submit publicly visible customer reviews of events on New York City Theater: any information you post publicly using our Services will be publicly available to anyone else who visits New York City Theater.  

We are not responsible for your use of otherwise private personal information, which you make available via our Services, or the activities of other users or other third parties to whom you give or make available your information. For example, we will never reveal your email address to other users as part of the normal operation of our Services, but we have no control over you choosing to post your email address in a public location such as a message board.

We may contact you directly or through a third party service provider regarding products or services you have signed up or purchased from us, such as necessary to deliver transactional or service related communications. We may also contact you with offers for additional services we think you’ll find valuable if you give us consent, or where allowed based upon legitimate interests. These contacts may include:

  * Email
  * Push notifications
  * SMS

You can update your email preferences to control how we communicate with you or unsubscribe completely in many ways:

  * Replying with unsubscribe in the email subject
  * Clicking the Unsubscribe, Update preferences or Edit your subscription links in the emails we send you
  * Visiting the User Account area on our Website, logging in and choosing My Preferences or Unsubscribe from the menu options

If you have any problems updating your preferences, please contact support@newyorkcitytheatre.com and we’ll help you make sure you only receive the communications that you want to receive.

We may share your personal data with third parties with which we have partnered to allow you to integrate their services into our own Services, and with trusted third party service providers as necessary for them to perform services on our behalf, such as:

  * Communicating with you, such as by email or push notification
  * Processing credit card payments
  * Fulfillment of ticket purchases
  * Serving advertisements
  * Conducting contests or surveys
  * Performing analysis of our Services and customers’ demographics
  * Customer relationship management

We only share your personal data as necessary for any third party to provide the services as requested or as needed on our behalf. These third parties (and any subcontractors) are subject to strict data processing terms and conditions and are prohibited from utilising, sharing or retaining your personal data for any other purpose than as they have been specifically contracted for (or without your consent).

#### Processing & fulfillment of ticket purchases

Ticket fulfilment services relating to our Services may be handled by one of our ticket fulfilment partners including but not limited to: Ticketmaster, Goldstar, London Theatre Direct, Love Theatre, Ingresso, Encore tickets, TicketNetwork and Vivid Seats.  We will share your details with our ticket fulfilment partners only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing & fulfilling your ticket purchase and dealing with queries and complaints relating to your purchase. You can find information about their privacy policies and practices at:  [Ticketmaster](https://www.ticketmaster.co.uk/legal/privacy.html), [Goldstar](https://www.goldstar.com/company/privacy), [London Theatre Direct](https://www.londontheatredirect.com/privacy-policy), [Love Theatre](https://www.lovetheatre.com/information/privacy-policy), [Ingresso](https://londontheatreland.ticketswitch.com/site/t_and_c/), [Encore tickets](https://www.encoretickets.co.uk/privacy-policy), [TicketNetwork](https://www.ticketnetwork.com/en/policies) and [Ticket Fulfillment Services](https://www.vividseats.com/privacy.html)

#### Processing financial transactions

Financial transactions relating to our Services may be handled by one of our payment service providers including but not limited to: Our bank, Paypal, Apple Pay and Braintree. We will share transaction data with our payment service providers or bank only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing your payments, refunding such payments, transferring money to you, and dealing with queries and complaints relating to such payments, refunds and transfers. You can find information about their privacy policies and practices at:  [Paypal](https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full), [Apple Pay](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT203027), [Braintree](https://www.braintreepayments.com/en-gb/legal/braintree-privacy-policy)

The hosting, analytics, email sending and other technical provisions for our website and mobile app are situated in the United States. If you utilise our Services from a country other than the United States, your communications with us may result in transferring your personal data across international borders. The European Commission has made an “adequacy decision” with respect to the data protection laws of the United States. Transfers to the United States will be protected by appropriate safeguards.

The U.S.-based Data Processors who process and store the bulk of our data participate in the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and we make participation in the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and similar programmes in other territories a top priority when selecting data processing vendors.

Your data may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, delivering our Services to you or the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (such as subpoena requests), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, we will take reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of legal process.

We use multiple analytics tools provided by service partners such as Google Analytics to collect information about how you interact with our website or mobile applications, including what pages you visit, what site you visited prior to visiting our website, how much time you spend on each page, what operating system and web browser you use and network and IP information. We use the information provided by these tools to improve our Services. These tools place persistent cookies in your browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our website. Each cookie cannot be used by anyone other than the service provider (e.g. Google for Google Analytics). The information collected from the cookie may be transmitted to and stored by these service partners on servers in a country other than the country in which you reside. Though information collected does not include personal data such as name, address, etc., the information collected is used and shared by these service provider in accordance with their individual privacy policies. You can control the technologies we use by managing your settings through our [Cookie Policy](https://www.newyorkcitytheatre.com/privacy-cookies/) or the “cookie banners” that may be presented (depending on URL of website visited) when you first visit our web pages, or by utilising settings in your browser or third-party tools. Please bear in mind that refusing or deleting some cookies may make it impossible for us to provide our Services to you.

Targeted ads or interest-based offers may be presented to you based on your activities on our webpages, and other websites. These offers will display as varying product banners presented to you while browsing. We also partner with third parties to manage our advertising on our webpages and other websites.  Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information such activities in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests, and to measure advertising effectiveness. View the **Advertising Section (3.2)** of our Cookie Policy to see more details about our advertising partners, their cookies and how to manage them. 

Alternatively you can opt out of interest-based advertising by visiting:

  * [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) (EU Only)

Please note that opting out will only prevent targeted ads an you will continue to receive generic, non-targeted ads.

Our website and our mobile applications contain links to third-party websites, for example [opentable.com](https://www.opentable.com/legal/privacy-policy) for pre-theatre dining, [parkwhiz](http://www.parkwhiz.com/support/privacy/) for parking and [booking.com](https://www.booking.com/content/privacy.en-gb.html) for overnight stays. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party sites.  Please read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

## 6\. How you can change or delete the information we hold about you

You can unsubscribe from any or all of our newsletters or your My Theatreland account by using our unsubscribe page at <https://www.newyorkcitytheatre.com/users/newsletters/unsubscribe/>, by clicking the link at the top of any of our emails or replying with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line.

Our account settings include email preferences so you can enable or disable the different kinds of emails we send to you.

If you can’t unsubscribe or modify your communications preferences for any reason, please contact our helpdesk and we’ll help you.

If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.

## 7\. Your rights

At any point while we are in possession of or processing your personal data, you, the data subject, have the following rights:

  * Right of access – you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. Access to this information will be subject to an administrative fee of GBP 10 if your request is manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive.
  * Right of rectification – you have a right to correct data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * Right to be forgotten – in certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our records. Erasure will be subject to an administrative fee of GBP 10 if your request is manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive.
  * Right to restriction of processing – where certain conditions apply to have a right to restrict the processing.
  * Right of portability – you have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation.
  * Right to object – you have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing.
  * Right to object to automated processing, including profiling – you also have the right to be subject to the legal effects of automated processing or profiling.
  * Right to judicial review: in the event that New York City Theater refuses your request under rights of access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. You have the right to complain.

All of the above requests will be forwarded on should there be a third party involved in the processing of your personal data. In order to verify your identity should you request your data or information about your data, we may ask for a copy of your passport, driving licence, national identity card or birth certificate.

## 8\. How we take care of your data

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or those of our trusted partner services. We implement appropriate, generally accepted technical and organisational measures to protect your personal data against unauthorised or unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction or damage, including encryption where appropriate. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee 100% security of your data transmitted to our servers; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security to prevent unauthorised access to our servers.

If you have any questions about the security of your personal data, please contact us at [privacy@theatrelandltd.com](mailto:privacy@theatrelandltd.com) .

## 9\. How long we retain your data

We retain personal data only for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods:

  * standard email user retention policies:  until unsubscribed or repeatedly bounced
  * mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations;
  * for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; or
  * needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.

If you have any questions about the retention of your personal data, please contact us at [privacy@theatrelandltd.com](mailto:privacy@theatrelandltd.com) .

## 10\. Changes to this policy

We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website and in our mobile app. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy. We may notify you of changes to this policy by email or public notice on our website or mobile app.

## 11\. How you can contact us or a regulatory body

We hope this notice has helped you to understand how and why we collect and process your personal data to enable you to use New York City Theater.

If you have a query or wish to make a complaint about how your personal data is being processed by us (or third parties as described above) please contact our Data Protection Officer at [privacy@theatrelandltd.com](mailto:privacy@theatrelandltd.com) . This email address is actively monitored and we aim to respond to all requests within 30 working days, but usually much sooner.

If you live in the European Economic Area (EEA) or otherwise believe we maintain your personal data subject to the the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority in the United Kingdom, the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO):

Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO)   
Wycliffe House   
Water Lane   
Wilmslow   
SK9 5AF United Kingdom

+44 303 123 1113

More information can be found at <https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/>

  * Certified secure checkout
  * Phone customer support
  * 100% guarantee
  * We are an independent show guide not a venue or show. We sell primary, discount and resale tickets which may be priced above or below face value.
